William Gropper Papers
William Gropper Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Birthday scrapbook, inscribed "To Bill Gropper from his friends December 4, 1944" (Oversize 8)
Duboff, Samuel J. S6
Dubro, Ann S48
E. Spertner Jewelry Corporation (Norfolk, VA) S66
Ealand, Maria K. See U.S. Treasury Department
Eberly, May S62
Edmundson, Carolyn S40
Ehreneich, Bernard S38
Ehreneich, Emma S38
Elliot, Marian S62
Emma, Florence S62
Endore, Guy B1 (S22)
Engelman, Sue S30
Epstein, Beatrice E. S38
Estra, Samuel B1 (S27)
Evanoff, John B1 (S54)
Evans, Nancy S38
Evergood, Philip S8 (program)
Fabiola, Miriam S62
Fadiman, Clifton See Lidice (Czechoslovakia) Lives Committee (New York)
Fast, Howard S8 (program)
Fenton, Nancy S36
Fernandez, Eleuterio B1 (S57)
Ferrero, Frank L. S31
Field, Frederick V. S63
Field, Natalie S26
Finger, LouisB1 (S45) S26
Finger, Marya CarrellB1 (S45) S26
Finley, David See U.S. War Department
Finn, Dorothy K. S30
Firstenberg, Fred R. S40
Firstenberg, Helen S40
Fishman, Moe S3
Flau?, H. Lawrence S34
Fleischman, PaulineS40 S46
Floch, Joseph S28
Foley, Mary Sexton S29
Ford, H.M. B1 (S21)
Ford, James W. S33
Ford, J.O. See Hotel Sinnott
Ford, John Anson See Los Angeles Board of Supervisors
Foster, William Z. S33
Franceschini, Rocco See United Shoe Workers of America, CIO (New York)
Frankel, Nathan ? S30
Frankfurt, William See Industrial Insurance Agents Union, CIO (New York)
Frederick, Hyman See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Freed, Celia S36
Freed, Harry S36
Freed, Irving S30
Freehafer, Edward G. See New York Public Library
Freiheit, Manning S30
Freud, Ruth S65
Friedenthal, Louis S28
Friedenthal, Rose L. S28
Friedenthal, Ruth S28
Friedkin, Ann ? B1 (S65)
Friedkin, MeyerB1 (S65) S48
Fritchman, Stephen H. See The Christian Register
Fur Dressers and Dyers, CIOB1 (S14) S59
Furdman, Abraham S48
Furman, Felix S3
Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York) B1 (S22)
Gahagan, Helen S32
Gallagher, Leo See Katz, Gallagher & Margolis (Los Angeles)
Gamarf, Gustave S66
Gambell, Jose Gamiño S20
Garibaldi American Fraternal Scociety, IWO S68
Garlin, Martha S65
Garlin, Sender S65
Garraffa, Joseph See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Gartelman, John S71
Gebert, BoleslawS11 S34
Geleerd, Elizabeth R. S31
Gerasimov, Alexander S9
Gershon, Gladys B1
Gilden, Samuel S42
Giligian, Ann S72
Gleason, Lev G.S26 S41
Gleekman, Lewis W. S39
Glickman, Maurice B1 (S49)
Goff, Sophie S36
Gold, Ben S59
Goldberg, Ann S42
Goldberg, Claire Brown S36
Goldberg, Jack S36
Golden, Samuel See American Artists Group, Inc. (New York)
Goldfarb, Samuel S28
Golditch, Leonard E. S61
Goldman, Marcus I. S46
Goldman, Tillie S40
González, ErnestinaB1 (S54) S40
Goodman, J.A. Writers' War Board (New York)
Gordon, Max S42
Gorman, Samuel S48
Gormen, Rose S48
Gragis, Peter A. S46
Greater New York CIO Council S63
Green, Abner See American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born (New York)
Green, Nan S9
Greenberg, Dr. Sarah R. S26
Greenberg, Esther S38
Gropper, Gene S28
Gropper, Joe and Vera B1
Gropper, Lee S28
Gropper, William S12
Gross, ChaimS8 (program) S40
Gross, Renee S40
Guba, Selma S40
Gumpel, Morris S38
Gurr, Lena S38
Guttman, Alexander S36
Gwathmey, Robert S8 (program)
Haim, Bruce S40
Haim, Irving S61
Haim, Tillie S40
Halberstadt, Ernst S60
Halberstadt, Luba S60
Hall, A.W. See U.S. Treasury Department
Hammer, Dr. JuliusS26 S44
Hammer, Greene S26
Hammer, Rose S26
Hammer, Victor J. S26
Hanley, Neal S18
Hanson, Hilda S37
Haraz, Wojciech S34
Harburg, E.Y. S8 (program)
Harkavy, MinnaS8 (program) S11
Hart, Vivian S40
Hartgen, Vincent A. See University of Maine
Hasen, George S65
Hasen, M. S65
Hawley, Peter K. B1 (S27)
Hays, Arthur Garfield S40
Healy, Ned R. See Los Angeles City Council
Hellenic-American Fraternal Society of the International Workers Order (New York) S67
Heller, Abe B1 (S22)
Henderson, Donald See United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America, CIO (Phil.)
Higier, Martin M. S48
Higier, Ruth S48
Hill, Ricardo G. S14
Hirsch, JosephS8 (program) S15
Hollander, Mary Louise S34
Hollander, Max S34
Honig, CharlotteB1 (S21) S36
Hopkins, Rev. Dr. John Henry S49
Horowitz, Arthur S26
Horowitz, Joseph S36
Horowitz, Sylvia G. S36
Hotel and Club Employees Union, AFL (New York) S14
Hotel Sinnott (Paducah, KY) B1 (S37)
Howard University B1 (S53)
Huchthausen, Alice M. S34
Hudson, Roy S33
Hudyma, Mike S38
Hughes, Langston B1 (S57)
Ickes, Harold (Secr. of the Interior) S13
Industrial Insurance Agents Union, CIO (New York) B1 (S21)
Institute of Design (Chicago) B1 (S47)
Institute of Paper Chemistry (Appleton, WI) S59
International Brigade Association S9
International Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists, and Technicians (New York) S39
International Fur & Leather Workers Union of the U.S. and Canada, CIO (New York)B1 (S13) S59
International Jewelry Workers Union (New York) S39
International Workers OrderB1 (S21) B1 (S55) B1 (S57) S67
Iranian Institute School for Asiatic Studies (New York) S69
Isaacs, Stanley L. S8 (program)
ISIS B1 (S58)
Islez, Florence S38
Jacobi, Marie See U.S. Office of War Information
Jacoby, Lois S48
Jaffe, Irma S46
Jaffe, Sam S46
Jennings, Robert E. B1 (S57)
Jewell, Edward Alden See New York Times
Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order, IWO (New York)B1 (S43) B1 (S54)
Johnson, CrockettS8 (program) S48
Johnson, Mordecai W. See Howard University
Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee CommitteeS3 S11
Josephson, Barney S28
Josephson, Isabel S28
Josephson, Lucy S28
J.R. Watkins Company (Lowell, MA) B1 (S58)
Jungman, Erich S20
Junta Patriotica Mexicana S20
Justiz, Harry M. S64
Kahn, Albert E. S8 (program)
Kahn, Gordon B1 (S22)
Kamsly, Louise S44
Kamsly, Samuel S44
Kaplan, Joseph S62
Kaplan, Murray S62
Kasustchik, Daniel S34
Kathe, Betty S40
Katz, Gallagher & Margolis (Los Angeles)B1 (S27) B1 (S52)
Katz, Leo S20
Katz, Otto S20
Kaufman, Sara S. See Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order, IWO (New York)
Kay, Helen See State County and Municipal Workers of America, CIO (New York)
Kellman, Shirley S26
Kent, RockwellS8 (program) S20
Kenyon & Eckhardt, Inc. (advertising) B1
King, Nettie S40
Kisch, Egon Erwin S20
Kleinman, George See International Fur & Leather Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Kohler, Rudolph S37
Kohn, Ilanya S36
Kollenmeyer, Helen H. S28
Kosolov-Skalya, Pavel S9
Kostin, S. S9
Kozar, Mary B1 (S50)
Kramer, Dana S3
Krauss, Ruth S48
Kreymborg, Alfred See Poetry Society of America
Kroll, Henry A. S38
Krylov, Porfiry (Nikitch) S9
Kukryniksy S9
Kull, Ginger (Mrs. Brook) S48
Kuniyoshi, Yasuo S8 (program)
Kupriyanov, Mikhail (Vasil'yevich) S9
Kusman, Felix S11
Kyle, Constance S36
Labor Defender (IWW newspaper) S65
LaFarge, Henry See U.S. Treasury Department
Lake, Zeke See Chattanooga Times
Lamb, Leonard S36
Landau, Anni S41
Lane, Harold J. See United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America, CIO (Phil.)
Larkin, Jim S48
Larkin, Mona S48
Laufman, Sidney S8 (program)
Lawrence, Paula S31
Lawson, John Howard S8 (program)
Leach, Porter F. See Walls Have Ears (New York)
Lederman, Nathan. See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Lederman, Solomon. See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Leider, Ruth S71
Lengyel, Dr. Emil S33
Leredu, Andrew S39
Lerman, Bella S66
Lerman, Joe B1 (S27)
Leskow, Peter See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Leslie, Bob S26
Leslie, Kenneth S41
Lev, Ray S8 (program)
Levett, S.O. S60
Levi, Julian E. S8 (program)
Levin, A.B1 (S65) S44
Levine, Belle S34
Levine, Ben S42
Levine, Nathan S34
Lewenthal, ReevesS62 See also U.S. War Department, B1
Lewis, Beatrice E. S42
Lewis, Samuel See United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees, CIO (New York)
Lezberg, Joseph M.D. S67
Liberson, ? S9
Lidice (Czechoslovakia) Lives Committee (New York) B1
Lieber, Maxim S30
Lieber, Minna Edith S30
Liederman, Maurice S62
Lilienthal, Dr. Howard S69
Lilly, Margaret L. S30
Liptzins, Sam S30
Litchfield, Donald See Seattle Post-Intelligencer
Littman, Hy S48
Littman, Rose S48
Locke, Alain S47
Loeb, Dot S42
Logan, Louis S48
Logan, Sylvia S48
London, Kate S28
Lopez, James A. S71
Lopez, Jim See American Communications Association, CIO (St. Louis)
Los Angeles CIO Council B1 (S56)
Los Angeles City Council B1 (S54)
Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors B1 (S24)
Loth, Dave See U.S. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
Lovett, Miriam B. S28
Low, David S11
Low, Nat S42
Lowry, Jan Gabrial B1 (S13)
Lozowick, Louis S8 (program)
Lucchi, Pietro S59
Lustig, James S71
Mabry, Thomas D. See U.S. Office of War Information
Mackay, Elayne S62
MacLeish, Archibald See U.S. Office of War Information
Madison, Pete S46
Magaña, Manuel S68
Magazine House Publishers S41
Magyar Jövö (Hungarian daily journal) B1 (S53)
Mahler, Fritz S8 (program)
Mahoney, James Owen See National Society of Mural Painters (New York)
Mainberger, Adam See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Maletich, Rev. Strahinja See United Committee of South-Slavic Americans, New York)
Malone, Maud S42
Mandel, Estelle S62
Maniscalso, Steffi S62
Mann, Heinrich B1 (S51)
Manochor, Evelyn S40
Manship, Paul See Russian War Relief, Inc. (New York)
Marcantonio, Vito (Cong.) See U.S. Congress
Mardo, Bill S42
Margolis, Ben See Katz, Gallagher & Margolis (Los Angeles)
Marinos, Nick S67
Marron, Mary S3
Marshall, MarjorieS40 S62
Martel, HarryS38 See also Fur Dressers and Dyers, CIO
Martin, Charles S48
Martin, Fletcher S8 (program)
Maugham, W. Somerset S8 (program)
Max, Alan S42
Maymudes, A. See International Workers Order
Mazza, Richard See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
McAdory, Mildred S42
McCarty, Milburn Jr. See U.S. Treasury Department
McGee, Frank ? S39
Meadow, Hilda S30
Meadow, Leon S28
Meadow, Natalie S28
Melden, John S42
Melish, Rev. William Howard S8 (program)
Melnick, J. M.D. B1 (S65)
Merker, Paul S20
Merrill, Lewis S8 (program)
Messina, Joseph C. See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Methodist Church (Leonia, NJ) B1 (S66)
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures (Culver City, CA) B1 (S53)
Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York) B1 (S56)
Metzger, Ethel S3
Meyas, Chick S30
Meyer, Edwin Justin S40
Meyer, Manan Murr ? S26
Middleton, John E. S67
Miller, Louis M.D. B1 (S43)
Miller, Rosemary S38
Mills, Saul S63
Miloz, Alice S50
Miloz, Milton S50
Minnesota Labor (Minneapolis) B1 (S55)
Minor, Lydia Erbson B1 (S25)
Minor, Robert S33
Mitchell, Louise S42
Miterstein, Bessie B1 (S45)
Mitropoulos, Dmitri S8 (program)
Moholy-Nagy, L. See Institute of Design (Chicago)
Moldavan, Belle S34
Moldseva, Nicolas S34
Montgomery, Anne S70
Moore, Jennie LeGon S28
Moore, Phil S28
Moret, Enrique S63
Moret, Margaret S63
Morning Freiheit (New York) B1 (S68)
Morrison, Paul S29
Moscovitz, Sam S3
Motion Pictures Artists' Committee (Hollywood) B1
Muhlenberg College (PA) B1
Murray, Donald S50
"MW" (initials reversed) See unidentified
Myers, Beth S36
Myers, FrederickS7 (program) S8 (program)
Nard, Tibel S28
National CIO War Relief Committee (Los Angeles) B1 (S55)
National Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism (New York) S61
National Maritime Union of America, CIO (New York)B1 (S23) S13 S18 S63 S68
National Society of Mural Painters (New York) B1
National War Labor Board (New York) B1 (S27)
Negro Labor Victory Committee (New York) S64
New Age Magazine (Washington, D.C.) S62
New Masses S20
The New World (Seattle) S70
New York City CouncilS6 S72
New York Post S26
New York Public Library B1
New York State Association of Elks S63
New York Times B1 (S71)
New York University School of Education S33
Newman, Elsie S3
Nikolaun, Sam S34
Norman, Johanne S66
Northrup, Clark S. S72
Novick, Paul See Morning Freiheit (New York)
Nuñez, Juan R. S20
Nurenberg, Rubina S28
Nurenberg, Thelma B1 (S25)
Oaks, Gladys B1
Obermeier, Mike S14
O'Connor, John Jr. See Carnegie Institute
Ogull, Louis S36
Oliver, Rose S48
Osman, Arthur S34
Ostrower, Jack S38
Otero, Carmen S11
Page, Charles See Motion Pictures Artists' Committee (Hollywood)
Paine, Lola S42
Paine, Rose Chandler B1 (S19)
Pais, Emanuel ? S38
Palant, Meriam S26
Papanek, Dr. Jan See Czechoslovak Information Service (New York)
Parcal Mary L. S62
Parees, Max See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Parker, DorothyS7 (program) S8 (program) S10 (program)
Parsons, Alice T. L. (Mrs. Edgerton) S32
Parsons, Bishop Edward L. S11
Pass, Morris S42
Patri, Giacomo S11
Pearlman, Amalia B1 (S45)
Peetrow, Samuel ? S69
Pennock, William J. See Washington Pension Union (Seattle)
Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission (PHMC) B1
People's Daily World (San Francisco)B1 (S13) S61
Perez, Constantino S68
Perfiliew, Eugene S38
Perlman, Lucille R. S36
Peterson, Frank S66
Pettus, Terry S70
Pfeffer, Max S44
Philadelphia Quartermaster Depot S6
Phillips, W. B. See U.S. Office of War Information
Picon, Molly S8 (program)
Pierera, Emilio S11
The Pilot (National Maritime Union of America, CIO) B1 (S13)
Pine, Geri S62
Pinner, Berna B1 (S33)
Pittman, John See People's Daily World (San Francisco)
P?kins, Bea S42
Platt, David S42
Poetry Society of America (New York) B1 (S51)
Polak, Hilda S36
Polak, N. S36
Polesie, Herb S26
Polesie, Midge S26
Pollock, Abigail S38
Pollock, Wakel S3
Polonia Society S11
Poor, Henry VarnumS7 (program) S8 (program) See also U.S. War Department
Pope, Arthur Upham S69
Posner, Esther S36
Poteat, Edwin McNeill See Colgate-Rochester Divinity School (Roch., NY)
Pottenger, F.M., Dr. See Pottenger Sanatorium and Clinic (Monrovia, CA)
Pottenger Sanatorium and Clinic (Monrovia, CA) B1 (S53)
Powell, Dr. Adam Clayton Jr. S8 (program)
Prago, Albert S38
Pressman, Lee S8 (program)
Pritz, Dora N. (Mrs. Carl E.) S31
Proctor, Jim S28
Proctor, Miriam S34
Proske, Jos.? S42
The Protestant S41
Quintanilla, LuisS1 S10 (program)
Rab?, Rose S40
Rabinowitz, Marcia S36
Rabinowitz, Mrs. L.M. S36
Rabinowitz, Victor S36
Rabson, Lt. Comr. M. L. (USNR) S38
Radio Research Laboratory (Harvard University) S60
Radoff, Elana S70
Radoff, Freda S70
Rajkovich, N.S. See Croation Benevolent Fraternity of America, IWO
Ramieri, G. Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Randau, Carl B1 (S27)
Raphaelson, Samson S8 (program)
Raymond, Harry S42
Refregier, AntonB1 S8 (program) S38
Reiter, Oscar Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Renn, Ludwig S20
Resnick, David S30
Resnick, Isabel S30
Rey, John See Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks and Assistants Union of New York
Rice, Lillian Lloyd S30
Rich, Daniel Catton See Art Institute of Chicago
Robeson, PaulS7 (program) S8 (program)
Robinson, Boardman S8 (program)
Robinson, Clara S40
Robinson, EarlS8 (program) S18
Rochester, H. H. S32
Rodrigues, Raymond P. S49
Roemer, J. M.D. S41
Rogers, Elmer, E. S62
Roland, Anna S30
Roland, Samuel S30
Rosenbaum, Mr. and Mrs. Hyman B1 (S45)
Rosenberg, Amy S47
Rosenberg, David S47
Rosenberg, I. See United Shoe Workers of America, CIO (New York)
Rosenfeld, Alice S67
Rosenthal, Mildred S61
Rosenthal, Mrs. A. M. S26
Ross, Shirley S36
Rossen, Robert S8 (program)
Rossin, Alice H. S38
Rossin, Edgar L. S38
Rotenberg, Sol See International Workers Order
Rouch, Ida S30
Rowan, Edward B. See U.S. Federal Works Agency; U.S. Treasury Department; U.S. War Department
Rubin, William M. B1 (S14)
Ruffner, Lester B1 (S14)
Russell, Rose V.S50 S64 S69
Russian War Relief, Inc. (New York) B1
Russin, Robert I. S62
Rycoff, Irving M. B1 (S51)
Saint Gaudens, Homer See Carnegie Institute
Saltzman, R. See Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order, IWO (New York)
Sandburg, CarlS7 (program) S8 (program) S10 (program)
Sanger, Eileen S. S40
Sannella, Lee S. M.D. S72
Sarkisian, ? S9
Sarton, George See ISIS
Savitsky, G. S9
Scheer, Nancy S65
Scheneidernau, Betty S40
Schenk, Pepi S62
Schlesinger, Frank S59
Schneider, Isidor S42
Schneider, Sylvia T. S38
Schreiber, Sidney S26
Schwartz, Herbert A. Jr. See U.S. Treasury Department
Schwartz, Josephine S30
Schweiger, Sol See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Schweitzer, Rose M. S30
Scudder, Vida D. B1 (S29)
Seattle CIO Council S37
Seattle Post-Intelligencer B1
Seaver, Edwin S69
Seiler, Willy B1 (S42)
Selvin, Minnie Frank S71
Shafritz, Morris See International Workers Order
Shain, Mac A. S34
Shain, Rosa S34
Shapiro, David (Dr. and Mrs.) B1 (S45)
Sherman, Florentine, S. S48
Shevsov, Captain OrrestS7 (program) S8 (program) S10 (program)
Shields, Art S26
Shoemaker, Henry W. See Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission (PHMC)
Shukhmin, P.M. S9
Shumlin, HermanB1 (S22) S8 (program)
Silver, Michael S64
Simon, Helen S42
Singer, Laura S50
Singer, Maxwell S50
Sirianni, Francesco B1 (S57)
Skiba, Emil See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Slate, Marie S36
Slater, Dab S36
Slobodkin, LouisB1 (S52) S8 (program)
Smith, JessicaS42 S48
Society of Cultural Relations (USSR) S9
Sokolov, Nikolay (Aleksandrovich) S9
Solovyov, ? S9
Soloway, Irving H. S44
Sommers, Diane S30
Sondergaard, Gale S8 (program)
Sotomayer, Antonio S17
Soviet Russia Today (New York) S42
Soyer, Ida S38
Soyer, MosesS8 (program) S38
Soyer, Raphael S8 (program)
Spector, Marjorie S36
Speigal, Betty S28
Speigal, Eda S28
Spencer, Niles S28
Sperber, Dr. Perry B1 (S33)
Spertner, H.B. (Mrs.) S66
Spiegal, Walter E. S28
Stanek, Julia S64
Stanley, Edward See U.S. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
Stase, George ? S34
State County & Municipal Workers of America, CIO (New York) B1 (S52)
Stefansson, Vilhjalmur S8 (program)
Steig, William "Bill"S8 (program) S43
Steinbeck, John See U.S. War Department
Steinke, Herbert A. See Albany Print Club
Stepanian, Gabe See J.R. Watkins Company
Stock, Alexander S34
Stone, Harriet S62
Stone, Victoria S28
Strand, Paul B1 (S58)
Strauss, Arnold F. S41
Strauss, Marjorie S. S41
Strauss, Mark S48
Studio Morris Topchevsky S6
Stutz, Hyman S36
Sues, Ilona RalfB1 (S37) S8 (program)
Suller, Dean S30
Sullivan, Glenda S30
Surbeck, John S59
Suskind, George S42
Swerdlove, Harry B1 (S65)
Szyk, ArthurS8 (program) S38
Szyk, Julia S38
Tabb, Roslyn S28
Tamaris, Helen S8 (program)
Tannard, Madeline B1 (S43)
TASS Window Artists (USSR) S9
Teachers Union (New York)S64 S69
Teichware, David S50
Teichware, Sabrina S50
Tendi?, Antonio S38
Terry, David S40
Thomas, Maxine Smith S34
Thompson, Louise See International Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Thompson, Robert S33
Tiller, Dixie S69
Tobias, Dr. Channing H. S8 (program)
Toledano, Margaret LombardoS7 (program) S8 (program) S10 (program)
Topchevsky, Morris S6
Uhse, Bodo S20
Union of Soviet Artists of the USSR S9
Union of Yugoslav Americans S64
United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America, CIO (Phil.)B1 (S23) S69
United Committee of South-Slavic Americans (New York) B1 (S55)
United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, CIOB1 (S23) S71
United Federal Workers of America, CIOB1 (S56) S50
United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees, CIO (New York) B1 (S25)
United Shoe Workers of America, CIO (New York) B1 (S35)
University of Maine B1
University of Virginia B1 (S37)
Untermeyer, Jean Starr S26
U.S. Bureau of Engraving and Printing See U.S. Treasury Department
U.S. CongressB1 (S21) B1 (S54)
U.S. Coordinator of Information (Office for Emergency Management) B1
U.S. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs B1
U.S. Department of the Interior S13
U.S. Federal Works Agency (Public Buildings Administration) B1
U.S. Office of War Information (Office for Emergency Management) B1
U.S. Treasury Department B1
U.S. War Department B1
Van Veen, Sadie B1 (S52)
Vanguard Press, Inc. B1
Varga, Magit See U.S. Federal Works Agency
Varian, Dorothy S40
Viglei, Aurora S30
V?novic, Mrs. Joseph S49
Voska, Julia S34
Voska, Rudolph S34
Wagner, Aaron See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Wagner, E. S38
Wald (k)man, Alice S34
Wallock, RoseB1 (S45) S28
Walls Have Ears (New York) B1
Ward, May McNeer S40
Washington Pension Union (Seattle) B1 (S51)
Watson, Forbes See U.S. Treasury Department
Webster, MargaretB1 (S29) S8 (program)
Wecker, Eddie See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Weingarten, Fannie B1 (S35)
Weinstein, BobbieS3 S40
Weinstein, JoeS3 S40
Weller, Charles F. B1 (S43)
Weller, Eugenia, W. B1 (S43)
Werner, Nat S62
Weschler, Anita S32
Wess, Gladys E. S26
Westin, Elliot S38
Weston, M. Moran S63
Wheeler, Margaret L. S44
Whelan, Grover See Worlds Fair Exhibition of Contemporary American Art Committee
White, Joshua S8 (program)
White, Rev. Eliot S41
White House: Roosevelt Administration B1 See also names of specific departments, e.g. U.S. War Department
Whitelaw, Elaine S38
Whitty, Dame MayS8 (program) S70
Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union S34
Wilcox, Mildred S31
Wilcox, Philip E. S31
Wilkinson, C? S28
Williams, Barbara S28
Williamson, John S33
Wilson, Helen S38
Wilson, John S49
Wilson, Mitchell S38
Wise, James Waterman S8 (program)
Wise, Louis E. S59
"WM" (initials) See unidentified
Wolfson, Marion S19
Wolfson, Sidney S19
Wolman, Aaron A. S31
Wolman, Minnie H. (Mrs. Aaron A.)S18 S31
Woodner, Ian S30
Woodner, Ruth S30
Woods, J.B. S40
Worlds Fair Exhibition of Contemporary American Art Committee B1
Writers' War Board (New York) B1
Yeller, Deborah S38
Yergan, Max B1 (S62)
Young, Art B1
Yudin, A. S30
Yuditch, Paul S67
Yutang, Lin S8 (program)
Zarian, Dolia S40
Zerner, Charles S48
Zerner, Mimie S48
Zide, Abraham See Furniture Workers Union, CIO (New York)
Zorach, William S8 (program)
Zugsmith, Leane (and Ann ?) B1 (S27)
unidentified correspondence/signatures S20 S28 S30 S34 S38 S40 S42 S48 S62